<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>index on rvdm.net</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in index on rvdm.net</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© [rvdm](https://rvdm.net)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 19:09:56 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello, world</title><link>/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 18:55:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;p>So, I guess this is another attempt at a website. I need one a bit more now, due to wanting to share some information on my &lt;a href="https://rvdm.net/bgp/">peering&lt;/a> setup.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For the site, I&amp;rsquo;m using the static site generator &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io">hugo&lt;/a> along with some tricks with Github Actions, Github Pages, and a reverse proxy to host everything on my own domain name without having to pay for things.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Should you want to set up a similar thing, the repositories are open.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>bgp</title><link>/bgp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 17:50:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>/bgp/</guid><description>&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This page is about AS57048 and how to peer with me. AS57048 is an ipv6-only hobby-ASN with no other purpose than to learn as well as to provide me with ipv6 connectivity in places where I don&amp;rsquo;t have it.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="general-info">General info&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>AS57048 runs on a VM on a &lt;a href="https://www.proxmox.com">proxmox&lt;/a> server co-located at &lt;a href="https://coloclue.net/">coloclue&lt;/a> in Amsterdam. I run a mix of physical interconnects as well as tunneled connections for transit and peering.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>General information on AS57048 can be found in a couple of places:
&lt;a href="https://www.peeringdb.com/asn/57048">peeringdb&lt;/a>
&lt;a href="https://bgp.tools/as/57048">bgp.tools&lt;/a>
&lt;a href="https://bgp.he.net/AS57048">bgp.he.net&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Good to meet you!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This page serves as a personal homepage where I can publish some content as well as some information about my personal &lt;a href="https://rvdm.net/bgp">ASN&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The rvdm.net domain name comes from the letters of my name - I&amp;rsquo;m Robert van der Meulen, and more info on what I do professionally can be found on my &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/robertvandermeulen/">LinkedIn&lt;/a> page. This website is a personal thing, so any and all opinions and content here are my own, and not related to my work.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>